Oh my gosh!
Don't you know I’m a Savage?
I’m a Killa who will break you, ae
I'm Killa, ae yang akan merusakmu
I’m a Killa 君を割る ae
I’m a Killa 너를 깰 ae
I’m a Killa Te romperé ae
I’m a Killa ฉันจะปลุกเธอ ae
I’m a Killa 將你擊碎 ae
I’m a Killa tàn phá ngươi ae
You're still hiding and hallucinating
Kamu masih bersembunyi dan berhalusinasi
まだ隠して幻覚を広げた君
아직도 가리고 환각을 펼친 너
Todavía te ocultas y desplegas la alucinación
เธอที่ยังถูกปิดกันและอยู่ในภาพลวงตา
至今還遮遮掩掩 施展幻覺的你
Ngươi vẫn đang ẩn nấp và hoang tưởng
Beat you up, We Holler
Pukul lah, We Holler
ぶん殴る We Holler
팰라 We Holler
The pegaría We Holler
ใส่ไม่ยั้ง We Holler
猛打 We Holler
Đánh đi We Holler
I'm not afraid of you, you, Hit you harder
Tidak takut padamu, Hit you harder
怖くない 君 君 Hit you harder
두렵지 않아 너 너 Hit you harder
Miedo no te tengo Hit you harder
ฉันไม่กลัวหรอก เธอ เธอ Hit you harder
無所畏懼 你 你 Hit you harder
Ta không sợ ngươi Hit you harder
Push me in, Deep fake on me
Dorong aku ke dalam Deep fake on me
私を押し入れる Deep fake on me
날 밀어 넣어 Deep fake on me
Me empujo Deep fake on me
ผลักดันฉันเข้าไป Deep fake on me
將我推進去 Deep fake on me
Ngươi đẩy ta vào Deep fake on me
To the unprepared stage
Di pertunjukan yang belum siap
準備ができていない舞台に
준비가 안된 무대로
A escenarios sin preparación
สู่เวทีที่ไม่ได้เตรียมตัว
推向尚未準備好的舞台
Một sân khấu chưa hề được chuẩn bị
Corner me in, Fake on me
Dorong aku, Fake on me
押しつける Fake on me
몰아넣어 Fake on me
Me acorralo Fake on me
ยัดเยียดเข้าไป Fake on me
Dồn ta vào Fake on me
Fake on me
Got everybody mock up to me
You shake me up so that I feel ashamed
Menggoncang agar merasa malu
恥を感じるようにメンタルを揺さぶっておく
수치를 느끼게 멘탈을 흔들어놔
Para avergonzarme me sacude la mente4
เขย่าจิตใจให้รู้สึกเสียหน้า
讓我感到羞恥 動搖我的心智
Hãy động não đi, để cảm thấy hổ thẹn
Cold spectators are collapsed, ae
Penonton yang dingin, ae yang runtuh
冷ややかな観衆 壊れる ae
싸늘한 관중 무너져 ae
El frío público Me derrumbo ae
ผู้คนที่ดูอย่างเย็นชาต้องดับสูญ ae
冷淡的觀眾崩塌 ae
Đám đông lạnh lùng sụp đổ ae
I can't stand you anymore, Say No!
Aku sudah tidak tahan lagi denganmu, Say No!
もう君を我慢できない Say No!
더는 널 못 참아 Say No!
Ya no te aguantaré Say No!
ฉันจะไม่ทนเธออีกต่อไป Say No!
無法再忍受你 Say No!
Không thể chịu đựng ngươi thêm nữa Say No!
Wait and see, I'm a little Savage
Lihat saja, aku sedikit Savage
覚えておいて私はちょっと Savage
두고 봐 난 좀 Savage
Verás yo soy un poco Savage
คอยดูแล้วกัน ฉันน่ะ Savage
走著瞧 我有點 Savage
Để rồi xem, ta cũng có chút Savage
Your Dirty Play
Play-mu yang Dirty
君のDirtyなPlay
너의 Dirty 한 Play
Tu Dirty Play
การเล่นแบบ Dirty ที่เธอ Play
你 Dirty 的 Play
Những trò Play Dirty của ngươi
I can't stand it any longer
Tidak bisa dibiarkan begitu saja
これ以上見ていられない
더는 두고 볼 수 없어
Ya no lo puedo ver
ไม่อาจทนเฉยดูได้อีกต่อไป
無法再坐視不管
Ta không thể để yên nữa
You want to break me
Halusinasimu yang
私を倒したがる
나를 무너뜨리고 싶은
Quieren derrumbarme
ภาพลวงตาของเธอ
想要摧毀我的你那幻覺
Thứ muốn phá hủy ta
Your hallucinations are becoming
Ingin menghancurkanku
君の幻覚がだんだん
네 환각들이 점점
Tus alucinaciones más y más
ที่อยากทำลายฉันลง
Là những ảo giác của ngươi, đang dần dần
漸漸成為建構你的理由
the reasons to construct you
Semakin menjadi alasan membuatmu bangkit
君を構築する理由になる
너를 구축할 이유가 돼
Se convierten en razones para edificarte
มันจะเป็นเหตุผลที่สร้างเธอขึ้นมา
trở thành lý do tạo dựng nên ngươi
I’m a Savage
I'll break you into pieces Oh
Aku akan menghancurkanmu berkeping-keping Oh
君を壊す 割ってあげる Oh
널 부셔 깨 줄게 Oh
A ti te romperé y quebraré Oh
ฉันจะทุบเธอให้แตกสลาย Oh
我會粉碎你 Oh
Để ta nghiền nát ngươi Oh
I’m a Savage
I'll crush you Oh
Aku akan menginjakmu Oh
君を踏みにじってあげる Oh
널 짓밟아 줄게 Oh
Te pisotearé Oh
ฉันจะเหยียบย่ำเธอเอง Oh
我會踐踏你 Oh
Để ta chà đạp ngươi Oh
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Get me now
Pegang aku sekarang
今 私を掴んで
지금 나를 잡아
Agárrame ahora
จากนี้คว้าฉันเอาไว้สิ
此刻就抓住我
Hãy giữ lấy ta
Or I'll become more Savage
Atau aku akan lebih Savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
아님 난 더 Savage
O si no más seré Savage
ไม่งั้นฉันจะ Savage กว่าเดิม
否則我會更 Savage
Nếu không ta sẽ càng Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Now I'm going to get you
Sekarang aku akan memegangmu
今は私が君を掴む
이젠 내가 너를 잡아
Ahora yo te agarro
จากนี้ฉันจะคว้าเธอเอง
現在我來抓你
Bây giờ ta sẽ bắt giữ ngươi
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
I can see your words
Kata-katamu terlihat
君の言葉が見える
너의 말이 보여
Veo tus palabras
ฉันเห็นจุดจบของเธอ
看見你說的話
Ta nghe được lời nói của ngươi
Your weakness Algorithm
Algorithm kelemahanmu
君の弱点 Algorithm
네 약점 Algorithm
Tus debilidades Algorithm
จุดอ่อนของเธอ Algorithm
你的弱點 Algorithm
Algorithm điểm yếu của ngươi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
MA ae SYNK
不要妨礙 MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
Jangan mengganggu dan pergilah, Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
No me molestes y vete
อย่ามาขัดจังหวะ หลบไป Savage
Đừng làm phiền, biến đi Savage
滾開 Savage
Mmmh Everybody looks at me
I'm used to it
Sangat tidak asing, bukan
慣れてるじゃない
익숙하잖니
Ya estás acostumbrada
ชินแล้วล่ะสิ
不是很熟悉了嗎
Không thấy gì quen sao
I should take a step back, I have to endure it like an adult
Harus mengalah, bersabar, bersikap seperti orang dewasa
譲って 我慢しなきゃ 大人らしく
양보해 참아야만 돼 어른스럽게
Cede debes aguantar como si fueras mayor
กับการอะไรก็ได้ ต้องยอมต้องทนแบบผู้ใหญ่
讓步吧 要忍住才行 像個大人一般
Nhượng bộ đi, ta đã chịu đựng như một người trưởng thành
I'm locked up in the glass
I want to play
Aku ingin bermain
私は遊びたいのに
난 놀고 싶은데
Pero yo quiero jugar
ทั้งๆ ที่ฉันเองก็อยากสนุก
我還想玩
Ta cũng muốn chơi nhưng
Such a horrible expectation
Penantian yang sangat menakutkan
ものすごい期待
너무 끔찍한 기대
Una expectativa demasiada atroz
กลับมีแต่ความคาดหวังที่น่าขนลุกจนเกินไป
太可怕的期待
Sự kỳ vọng khủng khiếp
I'm locked up in that hallucination frame
Kurung aku di dalam sangkar yang penuh halusinasi
そんな幻覚の枠に私を押し込めておく
그런 환각 틀에 나를 가둬 놔
En ese molde de alucinaciones me encierras
ขังฉันไว้ในกรอบลวงตาเช่นนั้น
將我困在那幻覺的框架中
Đã nhốt ta lại trong khung ảo giác đó
I'm going to KWANGYA, Game in
I'm going ke KWANGYA Game in
I'm going KWANGYAへ Game in
I'm going 광야로 Game in
I'm going a KWANGYA Game in
I'm going KWANGYA Game in
I'm going 朝向 KWANGYA Game in
I'm going vào KWANGYA Game in
Defeating a subtle alienation
Kalahkan tindakan mengadu domba yang licik
倒す 巧みな離間
물리쳐 교묘한 이간질
Rechazo la astuta enemistad
เอาชนะความแปลกแยกที่แยบยล
戰勝巧妙的離間計
Xua đuổi kẻ ly gián gian xảo
And making me drift apart from my ae
And yang membuataku menjauh dari my ae
And my aeから遠ざからせる
And my ae로부터 멀어지게 만들
And my ae lo que me aleje
And my ae ต้องไกลออกไป
And my 從ae開始 漸漸疏遠
And, làm ta phải xa cách my ae
Your satisfying Trick
Trick-mu yang penuh kebanggan
会心に満ちた君の Trick
회심찬 네 Trick
Lleno de orgullo tu Trick
สิ่งที่น่าพอใจของเธอ Trick
居心叵測的你 Trick
Trick với đầy sự khoái chí của ngươi
We gone KWANGYA, Game in
We gone ke KWANGYA Game in
We gone KWANGYAへ Game in
We gone 광야로 Game in
We gone al KWANGYA Game in
We gone สู่KWANGYA Game in
We gone 朝向 KWANGYA Game in
We gone vào KWANGYA Game in
Cut it down, my sword of light
Potong, pedang cahayaku
切ってしまえ 私の光の剣
베어버려 내 빛의 검
Corta mi espada de luz
เฉือนทิ้งไป ดาบแห่งแสงของฉัน
劃開我的光之劍
Chém, thanh kiếm ánh sáng của ta
To you who is damaged
Kepadamu yang mengalami kerusakan
ダメージを受けた君に
데미지를 입은 네게
A ti que dañado estás
ลั่นหมัดใส่เธอที่ได้รับบาดเจ็บ
對受到 打擊的你
Gửi đến ngươi, kẻ phải nếm chịu vết thương này
It's a merciless punch
Pukulan tanpa ampun
情け容赦ないパンチ
인정사정 볼 것 없는 펀치
Despiadadamente es el golpe
โดยไร้ความเห็นใจ
毫不留情地出擊
Một cú đấm không có tình người
See? I'm a little Savage
Lihat itu, aku sedikit Savage
ほら 私はちょっと Savage
그것 봐 난 좀 Savage
Te lo dije yo soy un poco Savage
เห็นไหมล่ะ ว่าฉัน Savage
走著瞧 我有點 Savage
Nhìn xem, ta cũng có chút Savage
I block your regenerative power
Aku menghambat kemampuan reproduksimu
君の再生力を防ぐ
너의 재생력을 막아
Bloqueo tu habilidad de regenerar
ขัดขวางการคืนชีพของเธอ
阻斷你的再生力
Ngăn chặn sự tái sinh của ngươi
I distract you, I leave you out
Mengganggunya
乱しておく 抜けて置く
흐트러놔 빼놔
Lo estorbo lo saco
ก่อความวุ่นวายกระจายไป
弄亂 去除
Làm cho tan toác, làm cho hết hồn
Don't forget, this is KWANGYA
Jangan lupa, di sini adalah KWANGYA
忘れないで ここはKWANGYA
잊지 말아 여긴 바로 광야
No te olvides aquí es KWANGYA
อย่าลืมว่าที่นี่คือKWANGYA
別忘了 這裡就是KWANGYA
Đừng quên nơi đây là KWANGYA
I control your time and space
Aku yang mengontrol waktu dan tempatmu
君の時空間は 私が好きなように
너의 시공간은 내 뜻대로
Tu tiempo y espacio lo controlo yo
ห้วงเวลาของเธอเป็นไปตามใจฉัน
我能隨心所欲控制你的時空
Thời gian và không gian của ngươi sẽ do ta kiểm soát
Make It break it
I’m a Savage
I'll break you into pieces Oh
Aku akan menghancurkanmu berkeping-keping Oh
君を壊す 割ってあげる Oh
널 부셔 깨 줄게 Oh
A ti te romperé y quebraré Oh
ฉันจะทุบเธอให้แตกสลาย Oh
我會粉碎你 Oh
Để ta nghiền nát ngươi Oh
I’m a Savage
I'll crush you Oh
Aku akan menginjakmu Oh
君を踏みにじってあげる Oh
널 짓밟아 줄게 Oh
Te pisotearé Oh
ฉันจะเหยียบย่ำเธอเอง Oh
我會踐踏你 Oh
Để ta chà đạp ngươi Oh
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Get me now
Pegang aku sekarang
今 私を掴んで
지금 나를 잡아
Agárrame ahora
จากนี้คว้าฉันเอาไว้สิ
此刻就抓住我
Hãy giữ lấy ta
Or I'll become more Savage
Atau aku akan lebih Savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
아님 난 더 Savage
O si no más seré Savage
ไม่งั้นฉันจะ Savage กว่าเดิม
否則我會更 Savage
Nếu không ta sẽ càng Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Now I'm going to get you
Sekarang aku akan memegangmu
今は私が君を掴む
이젠 내가 너를 잡아
Ahora yo te agarro
จากนี้ฉันจะคว้าเธอเอง
現在我來抓你
Bây giờ ta sẽ bắt giữ ngươi
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
I can see your words
Kata-katamu terlihat
君の言葉が見える
너의 말이 보여
Veo tus palabras
ฉันเห็นจุดจบของเธอ
看見你說的話
Ta nghe được lời nói của ngươi
Your weakness Algorithm
Algorithm kelemahanmu
君の弱点 Algorithm
네 약점 Algorithm
Tus debilidades Algorithm
จุดอ่อนของเธอ Algorithm
你的弱點 Algorithm
Algorithm điểm yếu của ngươi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
MA ae SYNK
不要妨礙 MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
Jangan mengganggu dan pergilah, Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
No me molestes y vete
อย่ามาขัดจังหวะ หลบไป Savage
Đừng làm phiền, biến đi Savage
滾開 Savage
You are the one who protected me when I was in trouble
Kamulah yang melindungiku dari bahaya
危機に陥った私を守ってくれたのは君だった
위기에 빠진 날 지켜준 건 너였어
En peligro estaba y tú me protegiste
เธอคือคนที่ปกป้องฉันจากวิกฤต
是你守護深陷危機的我
Bạn đã bảo vệ tôi khỏi hiểm nguy
My naevis we love U
My victory, one SYNK DIVE
My victory, SYNK DIVE satu-satunya
My victory 一つの SYNK DIVE
My victory 하나의 SYNK DIVE
My victory es un SYNK DIVE
My victory หนึ่งเดียว SYNK DIVE
My victory 合而為一的 SYNK DIVE
My victory chỉ có một SYNK DIVE
All the opportunities you've created
Kamu membuat semua kesempatan
全て君が作ってくれたチャンスだってこと
모두 네가 만들어준 기회란 거
Es todo una oportunidad que tú creaste
โอกาสทั้งหมดที่เธอสร้างขึ้นมา
都是你創造的機會
Mọi cơ hội là do bạn mang đến
I know your sacrifices Oh
My naevis we love U
I know, we'll make sure to find your memories
Aku tahu, kami pasti akan mencari kembali ingatanmu
分かる 私たちは必ず君の記憶を探してあげる
알아 우린 반드시 네 기억들을 찾아줄게
Lo sé Tus recuerdos buscaremos como sea
ฉันรู้ ว่าเราจะพบความทรงจำของเธอแน่ๆ
我知道 我們一定會幫你找到記憶
Tôi biết mà, chúng tôi nhất định sẽ tìm lại ký ức cho bạn
Let's meet surely after the resurrection
Kita akan bertemu setelah kebangkitan
私たちは会える きっと復活 その次
우린 만나 꼭 부활 그다음
Nos encontraremos sin fuelta luego de la resurrección
เราจะได้พบกันและคืนชีพต่อไป
我們一定要相見 在復活之後
Chúng ta nhất định sẽ gặp nhau sau khi hồi sinh
Savage
Yeah~
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Get me now
Pegang aku sekarang
今 私を掴んで
지금 나를 잡아
Agárrame ahora
จากนี้คว้าฉันเอาไว้สิ
此刻就抓住我
Hãy giữ lấy ta
Or I'll become more Savage
Atau aku akan lebih Savage
そうしないと私はもっと Savage
아님 난 더 Savage
O si no más seré Savage
ไม่งั้นฉันจะ Savage กว่าเดิม
否則我會更 Savage
Nếu không ta sẽ càng Savage
Get me get me now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
Now I'm going to get you
Sekarang aku akan memegangmu
今は私が君を掴む
이젠 내가 너를 잡아
Ahora yo te agarro
จากนี้ฉันจะคว้าเธอเอง
現在我來抓你
Bây giờ ta sẽ bắt giữ ngươi
Now I'm a Savage
Gimme gimme now
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
I can see your words
Kata-katamu terlihat
君の言葉が見える
너의 말이 보여
Veo tus palabras
ฉันเห็นจุดจบของเธอ
看見你說的話
Ta nghe được lời nói của ngươi
Your weakness Algorithm
Algorithm kelemahanmu
君の弱点 Algorithm
네 약점 Algorithm
Tus debilidades Algorithm
จุดอ่อนของเธอ Algorithm
你的弱點 Algorithm
Algorithm điểm yếu của ngươi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
Steaming, it's steaming
Gimme gimme aku
湯気 湯気が立つ
김이 김이 나
Humea humea
อารมณ์ร้อนจนควันออกแล้ว
熱氣竄出
Bốc hơi bốc hơi
(Zu Zu Zu Zu)
MA ae SYNK
不要妨礙 MA ae SYNK
Don't bother me and bog off, Savage
Jangan mengganggu dan pergilah, Savage
邪魔しないで消えて Savage
방해 말고 꺼져 Savage
No me molestes y vete
อย่ามาขัดจังหวะ หลบไป Savage
Đừng làm phiền, biến đi Savage
滾開 Savage
Ha ha, What?